<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<changelog bulletedList="true">
    <changelogversion changeDate="July 16, 2015" versionName="2.5.3">
        <changelogtext>bug fixed</changelogtext>
    </changelogversion>
    <changelogversion changeDate="July 04, 2015" versionName="2.5.2">
        <changelogtext>bug fixed</changelogtext>
    </changelogversion>
    <changelogversion changeDate="June 29, 2015" versionName="2.5.1">
        <changelogtext>fixed a bug that causes the message "no server connection" when it connect to Internet</changelogtext>
     </changelogversion>
    <changelogversion changeDate="June 21, 2015" versionName="2.5">
        <changelogtext>Fixed a bug led to reload news</changelogtext>
        <changelogtext>Ability to evaluate news</changelogtext>
        <changelogtext>Added a subscription which turns off the ads</changelogtext>
        <changelogtext>Bug fixed </changelogtext>
    </changelogversion>
    <changelogversion changeDate="June 11,2015" versionName="2.4.24">
        <changelogtext>If you see this message - we are thankful for your patience, while we strenuously working on the new version of this app.
        </changelogtext>
        <changelogtext>We fixed more known errors. At the given momeтt, “app crash”   appears less than 20 times.
        </changelogtext>
        <changelogtext>We added the possibility to save your news only for 12 hours. It reduces saved News’ Data Base dimensions, and accelerate apps’ work on slow smartphones.
        </changelogtext>
        <changelogtext>We updated the correctness of articles links. Now when you click on links, your link will go where you expected.
        </changelogtext>
        <changelogtext>Sometimes, approximately in every 30 news, you can see the ad.</changelogtext>
        <changelogtext>Apart, we would like to thank to our unknown user, who Donate us  $4.99. Now, thanks to your help, only for 3 months we cross the line of $10 of gathered funds.</changelogtext>
    </changelogversion>
    <changelogversion changeDate="June 05,2015" versionName="2.4.20">
        <changelogtext> Bugs fixed </changelogtext>
        </changelogversion>
    <changelogversion changeDate="June 04,2015" versionName="2.4.17">
        <changelogtext>Now, every time, when the news updated, the ‘Top 5 notification’ generate,
            this displayed in notification area (on the top of smartphones’ screen). Thus, you will
            be informed about top news, without opening the application. Please note, that only the
            first news placed in the card. That’s why, in order to open all five top news, you
            should pull the bottom edge of the card.
        </changelogtext>
        <changelogtext>Actually, we do not know, whether this feature will be helpful in everyday
            use that is why, these "notification" can be turned off in application settings.
        </changelogtext>
        <changelogtext>"Top 20" is no longer the main screen, it is an overall newsfeed.
        </changelogtext>
        <changelogtext>Increased the amount of ‘default’ news sources.</changelogtext>
        <changelogtext>Fixed bugs, performance optimized.</changelogtext>
    </changelogversion>

</changelog>
